

# **AL JABIR**

### **PROFILE**

I am always as independent as I want to be. Growing up in a low-income family I am continuing my studies with difficulty. I love to pay my own expenses. I was attracted to electronics from a young age. Since that time, electronics have been the focus of my love. I am very interested in research. I will try to be a good researcher.

### **CONTACT**

PHONE:

+8801700500681

**EMAIL:** 

n.s.al.jabir@gmail.com

LOCATION:

Satkhira, Dhaka, bangladesh

### **EDUCATION**

### **Manarat International University**

Dept of Electrical and Electronic Engineering 31 August, 2022 - Continue

### Satkhira City college

5th May,2019 - 31 December 2021

#### Satkhira Government High School

5th January 2011-1st April 2019

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Smart Solution, IT Instructor

2019-2022

CCTV Camera setup, Computer Hardware Setup

#### Owner of a Farm

2015-2019

I had a bird and colorful fish farm. Where I kept more than 100 Birds of 4 species and 3 species of aquarium fish.

## **VOLUNTEER WORK**

#### Satkhira Blood Bank

Donating blood and collecting blood donors.

### Youth For Better Future Society

Providing free concessional sound education to the poor, helpless and needy children/students of all communities irrespective of their race, religions, cast. providing food, clothing, medical aid, libraries and other required facilities for them.

### **SKILLS**

Project Management

Photography

Teamwork

Classroom Management

Creativity

Microsoft Office